Ah, Kuro-chan.
あ、黒ちゃん
yes.
はい
long time no see?
久しぶり?
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
It's been quite a while.
かなり久しぶりだね
Take Kuro-chan with you.
おなりに黒ちゃん連れて
Is it a date today?
今日はデートですか?
that's right.
そうです
Kuro-chan has also been here for the first time in half a year.
黒ちゃんも半年ぶりだよね
That's right.
ですね
What do you think, Kuro-chan, Sakura-chan for the first time in half a year?
どう、黒ちゃん、この半年ぶりのサクラちゃんの?
He's my favorite person.
大好きな人だよ
What are you eating?
何食べてるの、それ?
Eating ice cream.
アイス食べてる
ice?
アイス?
You're eating some weird colored ice cream.
なんか変な色のアイス食ってるね
Is that good?
それ、うまいの?
that.
それ
delicious.
おいしい
delicious?
おいしい?
It's the one that crackles, right?
パチパチするやつでしょ?
Yes, it crackles.
そう、パチパチするやつで
Sakura-chan, what are you doing lately?
サクラちゃん、最近何してるの?
Something...
なんか...
I go to the library and study.
図書館とか行って勉強してます
You're serious.
真面目じゃん
You're working hard, studying as usual.
頑張ってんだね、勉強相変わらずで
I'm studying hard.
勉強頑張ってます
Hey, that's great.
ねえ、偉いね
What is Kuro-chan doing lately?
黒ちゃんは最近何してるの?
It's been hot lately, so I've been lazing around at home.
最近暑かったんで、家でゴロゴロしてた
Were you lounging around at home?
家でゴロゴロしてた?
You're living a busy life, again.
手だらけな生活送ってるな、また
Really.
本当に
You are.
あなたはね
Really?
本当に?
I see.
そっか
Has anything happened in the last six months?
この半年間で何かあった?
Sakura-chan.
サクラちゃん
What changes in particular?
特に変化は?
do not have.
ない
I was always studying hard.
勉強ばっかりいつも頑張ってたもんね
Hey.
ね え
He's serious.
真面目だもんね
This dress is so cute.
すげえ可愛いじゃん、この服も
So cute.
すげえ可愛い
It's getting hot already, before we meet properly.
もう暑くなったね、しっかり会わないうちに
It's already hot.
もう 暑 いです
Hey.
ねえ
It's already summer.
もう夏だよ
What are you doing this summer?
今年の夏は何する?
I want to go to the sea.
海に行きたい
What do you do in the sea?
海に何するの?
I want to take a photo pie.
写真パイ撮りたい
写真パイ撮りたいって
Don't go into the sea.
海に入んない
I can't go in.
入んない
What about Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃんは?
I also want to go to the sea.
同じく海に行きたい
I want to go to the sea.
海に行きたい
Kuro-chan, what are you doing?
黒ちゃん何するの?
I want to swim.
僕は泳ぎたい
Isn't that a pick-up?
ナンパじゃない?
Is it possible to pick up girls at sea?
ナンパは海でできるのかな?
I see.
そっか
It's so nice and sunny today.
すげえ晴れてていいね、今日はね
It's cold and delicious.
冷たくておいしいね
delicious.
おいしい
The ice cream tastes bitter.
アイスが苦いな
It's hot so it will melt quickly.
暑いからすぐ溶けちゃう
I need to eat it soon.
早く食べないとね
So, do you have any plans for this summer yet?
じゃあまだ今年の夏の予定は立ってないの?
I haven't put it up yet.
まだ立ててない
Isn't it standing up?
立ててないんだ?
But it seems like he doesn't go to the beach much just now.
でもさっきの時あんまり海とか行かなそうじゃん
My skin is pure white.
肌真っ白です
Summer has ended since I thought it was just the two of us.
二人なって思ってから夏が終わってる
That's what happened this year, then.
今年ことはってやつだな、そしたら
Have you ever been to Okinawa?
沖縄とか行ったことある?
long ago.
昔
There is.
あるんだ
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
The weather is bad so I haven't been to the beach.
天気が悪くて海は行ってない
That's right.
そうなんだ
So I'm only enjoying about 10% of it.
じゃあもう10%くらいしか楽しめてないやん
Okinawa.
沖縄はね
I see.
そっか
You wouldn't ask a rich black girl to take you there, would you?
お金持ちの黒ちゃんに連れてってもらわないでしょね
Then let's go together.
じゃあ一緒に行こう
Are you thinking of something naughty?
なんかいやらしいこと考えてないか?
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
a little bit.
ちょっと
Wander around.
あばよくまぐらって
But Kuro-chan, it's been a long time since I've done it, so what do you think?
でも黒ちゃん久しぶりやって、どう?
Can you see it?
見え?
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
You're so cute, Kuro-chan.
や っぱ可愛いね、黒ちゃんね
You've been studying hard.
ずっと勉強頑張ってたんだね
What did you do on your good night?
おやすみの日は何やってたの?
The day I did a internet prank with YouTube.
YouTubeとネットフェニックした日
What do you watch when you use NetFenik?
ネットフェニックしたら何見るの?
Attack on Titan?
進撃の巨人?
Wow, you're really good at it.
わーめっちゃ上手い
what?
何?
Do you think I'm old-fashioned?
俺を時代遅れの人みたいな?
It's a reorganization of magic.
呪術改編だ
Jujutsu Kaiju is a new thing this time, so
呪術改編は今度新しいやつというやつだから、
I will review it.
見直したりはする
You've already seen it all.
もう全部見たのね
I really like you, anime.
あなた本当に好きね、アニメ
Aso.
あそー
Kuro-chan, do you see something like that?
黒 ちゃんそういうの見る?
I think the manga would be better.
漫画の方が見るかな
What manga do you watch?
何の漫画見るの?
Don't say 2 people/months.
2人月と言わないで
Once upon a time.
昔昔
The generation is revealed.
世代がバレる
The generation will be revealed.
世代がバレるぞ
I read it a long time ago.
大昔に読んだけど
What about these days?
最近は?
Recently, I read Juvenile Training School Ushijima-kun.
最近は少年院牛島くんを読んだ
what?
何?
A skin-off of Juvenile School Ushijima-kun and Yamikin Ushijima-kun.
少年院牛島くん、闇金牛島くんのスキンオフ
Is that what you mean?
そんなのあんの?
It just came out the other day and I read it.
この間発売したばっかりで、それを読みました
You like bad comics, right?
悪い漫画好きなんだね、あなたは
That's Kuro-chan.
それが黒ちゃん
Sakura-chan, please stand up for once.
さくらちゃん立ってみてよ一回
You're in Hawaii.
ハワイですなあなた
Isn't your height a little shorter?
何か身長ちょっと縮んじゃない?
It hasn't shrunk.
縮んでない
Isn't it shrinking?
縮んでない?
The usual Sakura-chan?
いつものさくらちゃんか
Come on, let's do something because we're coming to the amusement park.
何かせっかくさあ、遊園地来てるからさあ、
Let's both ride something.
何か二人とも乗ろうよ
I want to ride.
乗りたい
Walk a little over there, that way.
ちょっとあっちへ歩いてくれ、あっちの方に
Do you like riding roller coasters?
ジェットコースターとか乗るの好き?
I love roller coasters.
ジェットコースター大好き
Can I ride?
乗れるの?
You can ride it.
乗れます
height?
身長?
I'm borrowing it.
借りてる
I'm renting it.
借りてます
Is there a possibility that you won't be able to ride due to height restrictions?
身長制限乗れない可能性ある?
You can ride it.
乗れます
Can Kuro-chan ride?
黒ちゃん乗れる?
I can ride.
乗れる
Aren't you scared?
怖くない?
It's not scary.
怖くない
Isn't Disneyland's Tower Optera scary?
ディズニーランドのタワーオプテラとか怖くない?
I absolutely love it.
全然大好き
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
What is that?
あれ は?
There's a Flying Dinator at USJ, right?
USJのさ、フライングダイナトルってあるだろう?
A scary one.
怖いやつ
I love that too.
あれも大好き
I like them all.
全部好き
Seriously?
マ ジ?
I like it from below the head.
頭の下から好き
That's really scary.
あれすごい怖いよな
So let's look for some attractions.
じゃあちょっとアトラクション探そうか
Is it a crane game?
クレーンゲームやろっか
yes.
はい
What, what do you want like this?
何この、こんな欲しいの?
want.
欲しい
liver!
肝!
Face liver!
顔肝!
Kuro-chan, please take a picture with your manliness.
黒ちゃん、男らしさを持って撮ってあげて
Put on makeup.
化粧入れる
Show me an example.
ご手本見せてくれよ
Oh, your eyes are amazing.
あ、目がすごい
I really don't understand.
めっちゃわかんないんだけど
Let's try it for now.
とりあえずやってみよう
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
やばいやばい
Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃん?
That's difficult.
難しいね
The arm is quite weak.
結構アーム弱いね
Now, can I take a picture?
さて、撮れるか
I'll go this far.
ここまでは行くんね
Absolutely impossible.
絶対に無理や
Just one last time, Kuro-chan.
ちょっとラスト1回、黒ちゃん
Show me the man's costume.
男の衣装見せてくれ
Buy it so far.
ここまでは買って
This is starting to fall.
これ落ちるようになってるね
difficult.
難しい
This is no good.
これはダメだね
I can't take a picture even if I spend 10,000 yen.
1万円やっても撮れない
I don't think I can take a picture.
撮れなそう
It's shrouded in fog.
霧に包まれてるね
cool?
涼しい?
It's cool but hard to see.
涼しいけど見えづらい
Kuro-chan is returning the ticket now.
黒ちゃん今チケット帰ってるから
It's hot.
熱いな
熱いね
Yes, please come.
はい、いってらっしゃい
Kuro-chan is bad at driving.
黒ちゃん運転下手やな
It seems a little difficult.
ちょっと難しそう
Poorly done.
下手くそ
poor.
下手
I hope to do it soon.
もうすぐやればね
Kuro-chan isn't very good at driving, is he?
なんか黒ちゃん運転下手じゃね?
Because it doesn't bend at all.
全然曲がらないから
While stepping upwards.
上行き踏みながら
We were bumping into each other really hard.
すげえガツガツぶつかってたけど
I thought it would be boring if I wore the original uniform,
原服したらつまらないかなってやったら、
It didn't hit me at all.
全然ぶつかって
That was fun, man.
楽しかったね、お前
It's a little different, let's try it.
ちょっと違うね、やってみよっか
This view is amazing.
すごいね、この景色
expensive.
高い
Aren't you scared of high prices?
高いと怖くない?
fun.
楽しい
It was amazing to be able to ride all the attractions.
アトラクション全部乗れて、すごいね
What about Kuro-chan?
黒ちゃんは?
It's not scary at all.
全然怖くない
Your face looks tense.
顔引きつってるよね
That's amazing.
すごいな
How long has it been since you last rode a Ferris wheel?
いつぶりですか、観覧車で乗るのは?
It's been a long time.
めっちゃぶり
It's a big deal, isn't it?
めっちゃぶりだよね
It's a big deal.
めっちゃぶりだね
This scenery suits me.
この景色が似合うな
It suits you.
似合うね
Sakura-chan, have you done anything petty lately?
さくらちゃん、最近ペッチなことした?
I haven't.
してない
Haven't you?
してないの?
Really.
本当に
I haven't.
してないんだ
why?
なんで?
I really don't have time.
時間がなくて、ほんまに
Is that so?
そうなの?
Yeah.
うん
When I hear voices like that, I feel like messing around a little.
そんな声聞いたら、ちょっといじったくなっちゃう
That's right.
そうだよね
Look at browser.
ブラウジャー見て
It's become a Ferris wheel for adults.
大人の観覧車になってるよ
That's already super high.
もうそれが、超上
It's on top so no one can see it.
一番上だから、誰にも見えない
I can't see it.
見えない
What naughty things do you do that you can't see?
どんなイッチなことしたら見えないの?
number one.
一番
Sakura-chan has beautiful boobs.
さくらちゃん、おっぱい綺麗だからな
Erotic?
エロ?
Are you listening yet?
もう聞くの?
I don't know.
分かんない
Kuru-chan, wrap up your skirt.
くるちゃん、スカート巻くって
beautiful.
綺麗
It's a fun amusement park.
楽しい遊園地だな
This is so cute.
すんげーかわいいな、これ
Erotic and cute.
エロかわ
Isn't this about the scenery?
これじゃあ、景色のことじゃないの?
The scenery outside doesn't matter anymore.
もう外の景色、どうでもよくなっちゃった
Really.
本当に
It's the highest place.
一番高いところなの
Open your legs.
足開いて
Kuru-chan, the amusement park is fun.
くるちゃん、遊園地楽しいな
It's fun.
楽しいね
Shall we go to the room right away?
早速部屋行っちゃう?
Then.
そしたら
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
It's been a long time since I've been nervous.
久しぶりで緊張するじゃん
I'm nervous.
緊張してる
Kuru-chan,
くるちゃん、
You can't help but look forward to it.
楽 しみで仕方ないでしょ
It will make your face look like shit.
顔にニアケ取るもん
Well then, let's look forward to it later.
じゃあ、後の楽しみってことで
Shall we finish uploading Kuru-chan?
く るちゃんのアップロード終わろうか
Akura-chan.
あくらちゃん
You've arrived at your room.
部屋に着いたね
I have arrived.
着きました
We had fun at the amusement park earlier.
さっき楽しかったね、遊園地
it was fun.
楽しかった
It's still cute.
相変わらずかわいいね
She's so beautiful.
すんごい美人だよ
It's been half a year, but has anyone had it recently?
半年ぶりになったけどさ、 最近は誰かに持ってた?
Isn't there a new day?
新しいデーないの?
do not have.
ない
No.
ない んだ
Even though it's so cute.
そんなかわいいのに
You're choosing too much, man.
選びすぎてんだね、男の人は
Are there any cool classmates?
同級生でかっこいい人いないの?
not present.
いない
He's not there.
いないんだ
I don't talk much.
あんま喋んない
I see.
そっか
Why aren't you talking?
なんで喋んない?
Better alone.
一人の方が
I see.
そっか
It's a Takane flower.
高根の花だね
It's been half a year, but I heard that this will be the last time.
半年ぶりだけどさ、 これがなんか最後になるって聞いたんだけど
some time ago.
さ っき
Is it true?
それは本当ですか?
It's true.
本当です
I don't like it.
嫌です
I feel so lonely.
すごい寂しいじゃん
Why do you want to end it now?
なんでもう最後にしちゃうの?
Because I'm moving.
引っ越しちゃうから
Oh, I'm leaving.
あ、僕行っちゃうんだ
Are you going this far?
こっちにこれぐらい遠いところに行っちゃうの?
yes.
そう
I see.
そっか
I miss Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん寂しいな
Then, Sakura-chan's skin can be seen.
じゃあ桜ちゃんの肌が見えるのは、
I guess it means I've woken up already.
もう身を覚めってことかな
Today is the last day.
今日が最後
Is today the last day?
今日が最後?
I feel really lonely.
すごい寂しいです、僕は
I wish I could have taken it about 10 more times.
あと10回くらいは撮りたかったよね
What is that?
それは何?
We're all moving.
みんなで引っ越すんだ
With my family.
家族で
We'll all move.
みんなで引っ越す
We're going to make some fun memories over there, from now on.
あっちで楽しい思い出作るんだ、これからね
I'm studying hard.
勉強頑張ってるしね
I'm rooting for Sakura-chan's future.
桜ちゃんの将来を応援してるからね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
But before that, I'm going to do something naughty today.
その前に、今日はエッチなことするけど
That light blue dress suits you too.
その水色の服も似合ってるね
Because it's the last time.
最後だからさ
Let's take our time.
じっくり撮ろうよ
cute smart tofu
可愛いスマートフ
On.
ォ ン
Then, could you please stand for once?
じゃあ一回立ってもらえる?
You look like a celebrity, don't you?
芸能人みたいな、 ルックスをしてるよね、
Sakura-chan.
桜ちゃんは
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What have you been playing with lately?
最近は何して遊んでたの?
I was at home most of the time, so today I played for the first time in a while.
ほとんど家にいたから、 今日久しぶりに遊んだ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
it was fun?
楽しかった?
today.
今日
it was fun.
楽しかった
tired.
疲れた
It's good to be home.
家にいることがいいじゃね
I get tired when I go out.
外出たら疲れるよね
Look behind you.
後ろ見てごらん
Just look back at your face.
顔だけ振り返ってごらん
Her hair is also very beautiful.
髪もすごい綺麗
You're so aware, aren't you?
すげえ気づかってるでしょ
Somewhat.
多少は
It's shiny.
ツヤツヤだよ
Try wrapping your skirt around it.
スカート巻くってごらん
A beautifully shaped butt.
綺麗な形のお尻が
The other day, did you have sex with someone for half a year?
この前あったさ、 半年前から誰かとエッチした?
I haven't.
してない
してないんだ
Kuro-chan said he didn't do it.
クロちゃんしてないってよ
Seriously?
マジか
Kuro-chan must have had sex the most times in her life?
クロちゃんが人生で一番エッチした回数多いんじゃない?
many.
多い
Kuro-chan is going far away.
クロちゃん遠くに行っちゃうよ
This cute Sakura-chan.
この可愛い桜ちゃんが
No way.
やだね
Then sew it on.
じゃあそれ上ぬいでごらん
Great body every time.
毎回素晴らしい体だね
She has a body that looks like it's on fire.
ほんと燃えるみたいな体型してる
West has a great threat rate.
ウエストすごい脅威率でさ
Her breasts are big.
おっぱい大きいしね
What do you think of Kuro-chan's body?
どうですかクロちゃんこの体
You'll want to eat it.
食べたくなっちゃうでしょ
Kuro-chan, you got kicked out of the amusement park, right?
クロちゃん遊園地からボッキーしたでしょ
Oshira
おしら
Look.
を 見て
Try it like a tea bag.
ティーバッグみたいにしてごらん
My butt is facing me
お尻向けたほ
cormorant.
う
Please take a snack on the sofa.
ソ ファーにおつまみ乗ってごらん
I'll ask you to give me more.
もっとプリってつけ出してもらう
Open your legs more.
足もっと開いて
Your butt is so plump.
プリプリだねお尻
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛いな
Now stand up.
じゃあ立ってごらん
Kuro-chan.
クロちゃん
Please touch my breasts.
お っぱい触ってごらん
Maybe again.
またかもしれない
Did it get bigger?
もっと大きくなっちゃったの?
It's gotten bigger.
大きくなったよ
Look at your face.
顔詰めてごらん
What do you think?
どうですか?
This beautiful girl's breasts.
この美少女のおっぱいは
Kuro-chan, that's the last time you'll see those breasts.
クロちゃん、そのおっぱい最後だよもう
Let's enjoy it to the fullest.
いっぱい堪能しようかな
How does it feel to have breasts for the first time in six months?
半年ぶりにおっぱい持ってどういう気分ですか?
Yeah.
うん
I'm still a little nervous.
まだ ちょっと緊張する
get nervous?
緊張する?
It's too painful.
辛すぎるよね
It smells good, right?
いい匂いするでしょ?
Please tell me what Sakura-chan's breasts smell like.
桜ちゃんのおっぱいどんな匂いするか教えてあげてよ
It smells sweet.
甘い香りするね
Sweet scent?
甘い香り?
Take off your bra.
ブラジャー取ってごらん
I'll take Kuro-chan.
ク ロちゃん取ってあげる
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
Those are really beautiful breasts.
すんごい綺麗なおっぱいだね
Sakura-chan, her boobs may not be bigger than before.
桜ちゃん前よりやっぱおっぱい大きくなってないかも
Really?
本当に?
I don't know.
分かんない
I feel like something is getting bigger in real life.
リアルになんかでかくなってる気がするぞ
Shichichi bastard.
したちち野郎
You're becoming an adult little by little.
ちょっとずつ大人になってるんだね
happy.
嬉しい
It's really big.
本当にでかくなってる
This is beautiful.
これは綺麗だわ
It's amazing power.
すさまじい威力だね
This is because it's erotic.
これはエロいからだぞ
Please stop hiding it with paper.
紙でちょっと隠すのやめてください
Show everything.
すべて見せる
Kuro-chan, suck your dick.
クロちゃん、ちくび吸ってごらん
What does it taste like?
どんな味しますか?
Please make me a chikubi bing.
ちくびビンビンにしてあげて
Does it feel good to talk about your breasts?
おっぱい喋られて気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだよ
Anything against it is fine.
反対もなんでもいい
Wow, beautiful breasts.
すんげえ綺麗なおっぱい
You're standing up.
ちくび立ってんじゃん
Touch my pussy through my pants.
パンツの上からまんこ触ってね
Do you know where your finger is touching?
指どこに当たってるか分かる?
Kuro-chan, should I take that off?
クロちゃんそれ脱いましょうか
You took off everything.
全部脱いだったね
I took it off.
脱いだった
Everything is cute.
すべてがかわいいよ
Place your right foot there.
そこに右足置いてね
One foot beside me.
そばに片足
Your pussy was fucked.
おまんことられちゃったね
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Let me sit there.
そこに座ってもらおう
In the middle.
真ん中で
Open your legs.
足開いて
Kuro-chan, open it for me.
クロちゃん開いてあげてよ
Get everything from the end right away.
最後から全部すぐに取りまえと
Even her pussy is cute.
おまんこまでかわいい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Hey, Kuro-chan.
ねえ、クロちゃん
I got fucked by your cute pussy.
かわいいおまんことられちゃったね
Look at Kuri's face.
くりの顔見てみ
Look deep into your nose.
鼻の奥まで映ってみ
It's getting better.
よっとうまいなってみ
Open your legs more.
もっと足開いて
Kuro-chan until now
クロちゃん今まで
My beautiful pussy was fucked
き れいなおまんことられちゃった
hey.
ね
I love your face.
顔 大好きですよ
ERROR
こっから正面見てごらん
Just before the letter M.
M字のさっきの
ERROR
クリムチューしたみな
Open it.
開いて
Can I lick Kuro-chan as I like?
クロちゃん好きに舐めていい?
ERROR
おまんこ気持ちいい?
Kuro-chan, taste it a lot.
クロちゃん、いっぱい味わえ
Sticking your tongue inside the hole.
穴の中に舌突っ込んでる
ERROR
もっとお尻つけやしとこ
Lick my ass too.
お尻も舐めて
Does your butt feel good?
お尻も気持ちいい?
It's this way.
こっちだね
Let's spread your pussy.
おまんこ広げてみしょ
Isn't it starting to rise?
くり立ってきたんじゃない?
ERROR
固くなってるでしょ
それもう一回スイープ
Pussy
おまん
How was it being licked?
こ 舐められてどうだった?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Yeah.
うん
Now, please sit down here.
じゃあ今度こっち座ってごらん
What is this?
これなんだ?
Chin chin.
ちんちん
Always penis?
いつもちんちん?
Yeah.
うん
Everyone please do it
みんなしてもら
cormorant?
う?
ERROR
半 年ぶりのちんちんだよ
Look at the photo.
写真見て
See the photo?
写真見て?
Yeah.
うん
Look carefully.
よく見てごらん
ERROR
優しく触ってごらん
Is it warm?
あったかい?
ERROR
なんか大きくなってきた
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってきた
You like big dicks, right?
大きいちんちん好きでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
ERROR
顔近づけてもらおう
If only I could make a moment like this.
こうやって一瞬がいいやつしたら
Grow up.
大きくなって
ERROR
くぼちゃん顔やしてごらん
This is also difficult to do.
これちんこもやりにくいし
Put this on.
これつけて
Do you want me to talk?
しゃべらせたい?
Yeah.
うん
Bring out the bell.
ベル出して
It makes me look naughty.
えっちゃな目がさせるんだよ
How about Kubo-chan?
くぼちゃんどう?
Sakura's mouth.
さくらちゃんの口が
You're punching people.
人をパンパンだよ
Is dick delicious too?
ちんちんもおいしい?
Okay, please open it.
よし、開いてください
It makes you look really naughty.
ほんとえっちゃな目がさせるね
Bring Kubo-chan.
く ぼちゃん持ってこら
Let's talk a lot.
いっぱいしゃべらせ
Don't talk by chance.
たまたましゃべるな
Give me more bells.
もっといっぱいベルを出して
Please clean all the bells.
ベルを全部きれいにしてあげて
While rubbing it with my hands.
手でしこしこしながら
Isn't it the best?
最高でしょ?
If you talk dick.
ちんこしゃべったらね
Rub it with your hands
手でしこしこしなが
and others.
ら
Be stiff with your hands
手 でしこしこしな
Ga et al.
が ら
Licking the bell vigorously.
ベルをいきとぺろぺろして
You like dicks, right?
ちんちん好きでしょ?
Try to feel good.
気持ちよくしてみて
Let Kubo-chan's skin do the talking.
くぼちゃん肌をしゃべらせ
It's clicky, right?
かちかちでしょ?
So then.
だからじゃあ
Let's stay in bed together.
よいしょにじゃあべっといてしようよ
hollow
くぼ
Chan.
ちゃん
I want to attack again.
また 攻めたいんだ
You'll be on your feet in no time.
すぐちくび立っちゃうね
You tasted a lot, Kubo-chan.
いっぱい味わったな、くぼちゃん
What should I do without putting one finger in there?
指一本入れてあげないでどうしよう
Make it feel good inside your pussy.
まんこんの中気持ちよくして
Isn't it tight?
きついでしょ?
You can only fit one finger in it, right?
指一本しか入んないんじゃない?
My fingers are full.
指でいっぱいつかれてるよ
Does it feel good inside you?
おまえこんの中気持ちいい?
Can I mess around with it a lot?
いっぱいいじってもいい?
It's so wet.
すんごい濡れてるよ
There are a lot of them.
つぼつぼ入ってる
Okay, use that.
よし、あれ使えば
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I cried.
泣いちゃった
Where does it feel good?
どこ気持ちいい?
It feels so good.
くりくりで気持ちいい
It's standing up.
くり立ってるよ
Please do it all the time.
くりにずっとしてね
It feels good here, right?
ここ気持ちいいでしょ?
Are you here?
おまえこんでしょ?
It's a kuribin bottle.
くりびんびんだね
Did you go with chestnut?
くりでいっちゃったの?
Kubo-chan, should I use that?
くぼちゃん、あれ使おうか
Is it okay to want inside a woman?
女の中ほしくっていい?
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
I remember.
覚えてる
I swallowed a lot.
すごい飲み込んじゃった
Do you see it stirring?
かき回されてるの分かる?
It looks like Chin Chin, right?
チンチンみたいでしょ?
Let's get some sleep.
ゆっくり寝きさせておこう
Your pussy is getting coated, right?
おまんこすんげん塗れてきたんでしょ?
It feels good.
気 持ちいいとかあるからね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Sakura-chan's mouth must feel good.
さくらちゃんの口気持ちいいんだろうね
Kubo-chan, avoid getting dicked.
くぼちゃん、ちんぽしゃくられるの避けなさい
Did you make it this big?
こんな大きくしちゃったの?
That's amazing, Sakura-chan.
すごいね、さくらちゃん
I think I'll fall about once in about 5 more faces.
あと5顔ぐらいで1回ぐらい落ちちゃうな
I'll have a drink with Kuru-chan.
くるちゃんと飲み合いこするから
Kuru-chan's head falls off.
くるちゃん、頭落ちちゃう
Don't push your pussy all the way.
おまんこいっぱい押し付けな
The face licking the dick is so cute.
ちんぽ舐めてる顔、すごいかわいいよ
Licking Kito.
きとうぺろぺろして
It's delicious, dick.
おいしいでしょ、ちんぽ
I'm licking all the places that feel so good.
すごく気持ちいいとこいっぱい舐めてる
Just with your mouth.
口だけで
Kuru-chan, you're so chubby.
く るちゃん、すんごいパンパンだね、
penis.
ちんぽ
It's all wet, just look at it.
じゅぶじゅぼうとなってて、すってごらん、
penis.
ちんぽ
It's ticking.
カチカチだよ
Try squeezing the spit.
つばたらしこしこしてごらん
You're doing naughty things.
えっちなことしてるね
Yes, I do.
うん、してる
Kuru-chan, try to get it on your tongue.
くるちゃん、舌からついてごらん
Have a lot of fun
いっぱいしゃぐらして
Ru.
る
Kuru-chan, are you here yet?
く るちゃん、もういるか
Go sleep there
そこで寝てごら
yeah.
ん
Take a look at the last pussy.
最後 のまんこ、さらじわってごらん
Take a look at it.
ちんちんでごらん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It makes me feel so bad.
すんごい気持ちを刺す
Can you see how deep it is?
奥まで刺さってるのわかる?
Yes, take a look.
はい、にしくついてごらん
Chin-chin, it feels so good.
ちんちん、気持ちいいんだから
Well, definitely rub it in.
まあ、絶対こすりつけてごらん
Come on, Kuru-chan, go upstairs.
さあ、くるちゃん、上でもいってごらん
Use your pussy to make it feel good.
おまんこ使って気持ちよくしてごらん
While showing off her boobs.
おきっぱい見せながら
So please go to Zengo.
そこで、ぜんごにもいってごらん
Grind it.
すりすりして
Try hugging Kuru-chan.
くるちゃんに抱きついてごらん
Her butthole is also fully visible.
お尻の穴も丸見えだよ
Let's take a look at the hole I made.
ぬいた穴見してみよっか
Kuru-chan, come from behind.
くるちゃん、後ろからつこう
Kuru-chan, it's from the back after all.
くるちゃん、やっぱ背面やろ
Bring your own penis and put it in.
自分でちんちん持って入れてごらん
You like this, right?
これ好きでしょ?
Kuru-chan, hurry up.
くるちゃん、だんだん早くして
Because I live on buns.
まんじゅうで生きてるから
Try straining it more?
もっとこしゅうがしてみ?
Kuru-chan, do your best.
くるちゃん、がんがんして
quickly.
早く
It feels good to hit deep inside, right?
奥まで当たって気持ちいいんでしょ、
this.
これ
Kuru-chan, make me feel good from behind.
くるちゃん、後ろから気持ちよくしてやって
Make a sexy face.
えろい顔してね
Kuru-chan, I'm here for more.
くるちゃん、もっとついたんよ
Look down and look at me from here.
下向いてこっちから顔見して
I went again.
また行っちゃったんだ
You don't have hands, do you?
手を持ってないでしょ
This is Kiktsuikuru-chan.
きっついくるちゃん、これ
Soooo cool
すっごいき
unintentionally.
つ い
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Follow me.
ついてごらん
Kuru-chan may have reached her limit.
くるちゃん、もう限界までかも
Tight.
きっつい
It's a carp, Kuru-chan.
こいのだしたな、くるちゃん
Make it a fitting spirit at the end.
最後にふさわしい精神をしてください
already
もう
Be careful once.
一 回、気をつかう
Lick my dick clean
チンチン舐めてきれいにして
hey.
ね
Can you taste the spirit?
精 神の味する?
Clean it all up.
全部それきれいにして
That dick was really hard.
すごい硬かった、チンチンを
Because I put it all out.
全部出したからね
Did it come out clean?
きれいにできたの?
Kuru-chan, I feel lonely.
くるちゃん、さみしいね
Sakura-chan, this is the last time.
さくらちゃん、これで最後だって
I hope we can meet again somewhere, Sakura-chan.
またどっかで会えたらいいね、さくらちゃん
Somewhere.
どこかで
My uncles are always waiting for me.
おじさんたちはいつも待ってるからね
I'm rooting for Sakura-chan's bright future.
さくらちゃんの明るい未来を応援してるね
Thank you so much, Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃん、今までありがとう
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
bye bye.
バイバイ